http://www.cedarshed.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONCedarshed is committed to protecting your personal information. The following outlines our policies and how we treat the information that you provide us.
In general, you can visit this website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.Information Collected:Our web servers collect the domain names, not the email addresses of visitors. There are portions of this website where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with information that you request. Such information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or email address.Use of Collected Information:Your domain name information is not used to personally identify who you are and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We analyze this information to measure how our website is being used and to improve its content.
When supplied by you, we use your name and email address to respond to your inquiries, or to process requests. This information may be shared with our Authorized Dealer network, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes.
We may share a limited amount of your personal information with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies, such as our vendors, use your personal information only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.
We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).Links to Other Sites: Cedarshed's website may contain links to other sites such as Cedarshed dealers and distributors or other Gardening and Home Improvement Resources. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites. Cookies: We do not use Cookies at the Cedarshed website.
Security of Collected Information: We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access.
We restrict access to information about you to those Cedarshed workers who need to know the information in order to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action. Unsubscribe: Our email newsletter has instructions on how to easily unsubscribe. Accessing and Updating Personal Information: We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or e-mail address. Our websites do not currently offer users the ability to update their own personal data, please contact us directly at 1-800-830-8033 or email sales@cedarshed.com to update your personal data. Contacting Us: If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy. Changes to this Policy: Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes.
Explore
Permits
Ordering
Shipping & Delivery
Site Prep
Foundations
Care & Maintenance
Warranty
